## **Jay Thomason**

#### **SUMMARY**

Dedicated IT professional with over 5 years of experience in technical support, looking for diverse roles that offer growth and skill development opportunities. Proven track record of providing excellent customer service, with foundational knowledge in software development and systems administration.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## ICT Support Officer | Calvary Health Care

September 2022 - Present, Melbourne, VIC

- Provided L1 and L2 tech support to a large organisation of 18,000 healthcare professionals.
- · Developed a user-friendly GUI application enabling swift retrieval of user information for help desk staff.
- Improved help desk efficiency by designing a one-click GUI tool to streamline system administration tasks.
- · Automated multiple stages of the user onboarding process using Power Automate Desktop and PowerShell, significantly reducing manual workload.

## L2 Desktop Support | Defence Science and Technology Group

August 2021 - June 2022, Melbourne, VIC

- · Provided L2 desktop, network, and system administration support within a secure scientific computing environment.
- Supported a variety of specialized hardware and software, ranging from million-dollar microscopes to complex Python development environments.
- Improved integrity of the asset handling process by implementing changes that reduced the risk of lost or stolen equipment.

## Project Support, L2 Help Desk Support | 5G Networks

May 2021 - August 2021, Melbourne, VIC

- Played a key role in the implementation of a comprehensive Microsoft Teams-based telephony solution.
- Contributed to a library of technical documentation for our product on GitHub.
- Developed and delivered a complete training seminar on our product.
- · Provided L2 help desk support to customers, promptly addressing critical server and network outages within 15 minutes.

## **Account Manager** | Technicalities Group Consulting

April 2019 - May 2020, Melbourne, VIC

- · Provided L2 help desk support for various ICT solutions, including hosting services, backups, network security, and more.
- · Cultivated relationships with our clients, gaining an understanding of their needs and requirements.
- · Conducted two informative training seminars, promoting our products and educating customers on cyber security practices.

## **PROJECTS**

#### **Home Lab**

- Orchestrated a virtualization environment with Proxmox, managing VMs and Docker-hosted containerized services.
- Developed an automated VM creation Bash script with pre-configured OS via cloud-init.
- Employed Ansible for automated server configuration and maintenance workflows.

## **EDUCATION**

## Graduate Certificate in Programming and Development | Swinburne University

Melbourne, VIC, 2023

## **COURSEWORK**

## Front-end Web Development | Swinburne University | React

2023

· Developed a complete application for a local football club using React. The application was acceptance tested and deployed live to a web server

# Organisational Growth and Innovation Capstone Project | Swinburne University | Teamwork 2023

• Developed a strategic plan to enhance an e-commerce store's product sales. Successfully led a team as a Scrum Master, facilitating team communication, conflict resolution and practicing servant leadership

#### **SKILLS**

Windows 10, Mac OS and Linux Support, Hardware & Software Troubleshooting, MS Office 365, Active Directory Management, Software and OS Deployment via SCCM, Mobile Device and Tablet Support, Mobile Device Management (Solarwinds, Intune), Network Monitoring & Triage (PuTTy, Wireshark, Auvik, Solarwinds Orion)